waytonikah.com 2011-12-06

# waytonikah.com® :- Kerala's No1 Muslim Matrimonial Website

---  
  
|  |   
---  
  
Our Lord! Grant unto us wives and offspring who will be the comfort of our eyes, and give us (the grace) to lead righteous. Qur'an 25:74

* * *

"A woman may married for four reasons: for her property, for her rank, for her beauty, and for her religion (and character). So marry the one who is best in the religion and character and prosper". (Bukhari and Muslim)

* * *

"The whole world is an asset and the best asset is a good wife" (Muslim)  

| 

This electronic website is being operated and owned by www.waytonikah.com This PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT is made/published in the internet web site to protect the user’s privacy and it is connected to our terms and conditions.   
  
---  
  
A user/member, when he is entering our web site after accepting our full terms and conditions of [www.waytonikah.com](http://www.waytonikah.com/) should provide the mandatory information, he has the option of not providing the information which is not mandatory. User/Member is solely responsible for maintaining confidentiality of the User Name/Identity and User Password and all activities and transmission/transactions performed by the User through his/her user identity/name and shall be solely responsible for carrying out any online or off-line transactions involving credit/debit cards or such other forms of instruments or documents for making such transactions. As such, while doing so any negligence of your act, [www.waytonikah.com](http://www.waytonikah.com/) assumes no responsibility / liability for their improper use of information relating to such usage of credit/debit cards used by the subscriber online/offline.   
  
[www.waytonikah.com](http://www.waytonikah.com/) is connected / link to service partners, such as servers/administrators. We may use your IP address and other information provided by like Email address, Contact name, User-created password, Address , Pin code, Telephone number or other contact number etc; to help diagnose problems with our server, and to manage our Web site. Your IP address may be also used to gather broad demographic information. And the information will be used by us to contact you and to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the web site. To receive such information, you accept for our terms and condition and privacy policy.   
  
Unless otherwise you give your consent, it doesn’t sell, rent, share, trade or give away or share with any third party. The users who enter into site such as Builders, Agents/Brokers or any individual has provided their contact information for advertisement on our portal then users can contact them at their request through us.   
  
Any changes in the privacy policy will be changed without any prior notice to any type of users, of our web site. We suggest you to review our privacy policy from time to time/ periodically, so as to see if any changes are made.   
  
[www.waytonikah.com](http://www.waytonikah.com/) cannot be held liable for any errors or inconsistencies. But we take every care to give you accuracy and clarity of the information.   
  
[www.waytonikah.com](http://www.waytonikah.com/) disclaims any and all responsibility or liability for the accuracy, content, completeness, legality, reliability, or operability or availability of information or material displayed on this web site by the third parties...   
  
At www.Waytonikah.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.Waytonikah.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.Waytonikah.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user?s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.Waytonikah.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.Waytonikah.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.Waytonikah.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Waytonikah.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.Waytonikah.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Waytonikah.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.   
  
Contact : [info@waytonikah.com](mailto:info@waytonikah.com) for further clarifications.
